A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- SB 784 (01) Marine Patrol Officers; powers (Box 36, Folder 7)
- SB 789 (01) Loss of Driving Privileges for Making a Bomb Threat (Box 36, Folder 8)
- SB 791 (01) Property Tax Exemption; Various Exemptions (Box 36, Folder 9)
- SB 793 (01) Baseball Stadium Authority; Entitlement to Income and Sales and Use Taxes (Box 36, Folder 10)
- SB 794 (01) Baseball Stadium; Local Admissions Tax (Box 36, Folder 11)
- SB 796 (01) Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority (Box 36, Folder 12)
- SB 798 (01) License Plates; Coverings (Box 36, Folder 13)
- SB 801 (01) Adult Abuse and Neglect (Box 36, Folder 14)
- SB 802 (01) Convicts as Witnesses in Civil Actions (Box 36, Folder 15)
- SB 806 (01) Practice of Dentistry; Cosmetic Procedures (folder 1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 16)
- SB 806 (01) Practice of Dentistry; Cosmetic Procedures (folder 2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 17)
- SB 808 (01) Medical Malpractice Cap (Box 36, Folder 18)
- SB 809 (01) Executive, Judicial and Independent Agencies' Bill Drafting Deadline (Box 36, Folder 19)
- SB 810 (01) Public Procurement Act; Certain Purchases by School Boards (Box 36, Folder 20)
- SB 814 (01) School Board Salaries; Various Localities (Box 36, Folder 21)
- SB 817 (01) Mandatory Connection to Water and Sewage Systems (Box 36, Folder 22)
- SB 820 (01) Potomac River Compact; Storage, etc., of Harvested Finfish and Shellfish (Box 36, Folder 23)
- SB 822 (01) No-Truck Route; US 17 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- SB 823 (01) License Plates; Reserved Numbers and Letters (Box 36, Folder 25)
- SB 824 (01) HIV Testing of Criminal Defendants (Box 36, Folder 26)
- SB 827 (01) Adult Protective Services; Competency Training (Box 36, Folder 27)
- SB 828 (01) Special Conservators of the Peace (Box 36, Folder 28)
- SB 834 (01) Natural Gas Consumption Tax (Box 36, Folder 29)
- SB 835 (01) Motorcycle Rider Safety; Training Courses and Centers (Box 36, Folder 30)
- SB 836 (01) Electric Power-Assisted Bicycles (Box 36, Folder 31)
- SB 837 (01) Subaqueous Permit Exemption (Box 36, Folder 32)
- SB 838 (01) Health; Radon Proficiency Listings (Box 36, Folder 33)
- SB 840 (01) VRS; Transfer of Member Contributions (Box 36, Folder 34)
- SB 843 (01) VRS; Partial Lump-Sum Payment Option (Box 36, Folder 35)
- SB 844 (01) VRS; Introduction of VRS Bills (Box 36, Folder 36)
- SB 847 (01) Threats; Penalty (Box 36, Folder 37)
- SB 849 (01) Health Professions; Medical Assistants (Box 36, Folder 38)
- SB 850 (01) Criminal Procedure; Compensation of Forensic Experts (Box 36, Folder 39)
- SB 852 (01) Filing Annual Return with Employee Withholding by Electronic Means (Box 36, Folder 40)
- SB 856 (01) VRS; Benefit Restoration Plans (Box 36, Folder 41)
- SB 857 (01) Registration of Dealers for Collection of Retail Sales and Use Tax (Box 36, Folder 42)
- SB 859 (01) Display of POW/MIA Flag (Box 36, Folder 43)
- SB 861 (01) Highways; Use by Motorcycles (Box 36, Folder 44)
- SB 862 (01) Restricted Driver's License (Box 36, Folder 45)
- SB 863 (01) Consumer Finance Act; Loan Amounts (Box 36, Folder 46)
- SB 872 (01) Gunston Hall; Certain Powers of Board (Box 36, Folder 47)
- SB 874 (01) Conditional Zoning (Box 36, Folder 48)
- SB 876 (01) Payment by Subdivider of Pro Rata Share of Certain Costs (Box 36, Folder 49)
- SB 877 (01) Capital Region Airport Commission (Box 36, Folder 50)
- SB 878 (01) Line of Duty Act; Claim for Payment (Box 36, Folder 51)
- SB 879 (01) Expungement of Police and Court Records (Box 36, Folder 52)
- SB 881 (01) Charter; Chesterfield County (Box 36, Folder 53)
- SB 884 (01) FOIA; Exemptions for Lottery Department (Box 36, Folder 54)
- SB 885 (01) Charter; Town of Wise (Box 36, Folder 55)
- SB 891 (01) Information on Marriage License Application (Box 36, Folder 56)
- SB 892 (01) Nursing; Licensure from Foreign Schools (Box 36, Folder 57)
- SB 894 (01) Appointment to Regional Industrial Facilities Authorities Board (Box 36, Folder 58)
- SB 896 (01) Municipal Electric Utilities; Restructuring (Box 36, Folder 59)
- SB 899 (01) Public Service Companies; Issuance of Securities (Box 36, Folder 60)
- SB 901 (01) Real Property Tax; Multi-Year Agricultural and Horticultural Crops (Box 36, Folder 61)
- SB 902 (01) Summonses Issued by Attorneys (Box 36, Folder 62)
- SB 904 (01) Forfeiture of Driver's License for Driving While Intoxicated (Box 36, Folder 63)
- SB 905 (01) Passing a Stopped School Bus (Box 36, Folder 64)
- SB 906 (01) Juvenile Detention; Maximum Extension Periods (Box 36, Folder 65)
- SB 907 (01) Request for Review by Medical Malpractice Review Panel (Box 36, Folder 66)
- SB 908 (01) Guardian ad Litems (Box 36, Folder 67)
- SB 911 (01) Commercial Code; Government Bonds (Box 36, Folder 68)
- SB 913 (01) Insurance Agents; Licensing (Box 36, Folder 69)
- SB 914 (01) Incorporation of Regulations and Amendments by Local Ordinances (Box 36, Folder 70)
- SB 915 (01) Charter; City of Norton (Box 36, Folder 71)
- SB 918 (01) Fees Collected by Clerks of Circuit Courts (Box 36, Folder 72)
- SB 939 (01) Local Real Estate Taxes in Northern Virginia (Box 36, Folder 73)
- SB 943 (01) Religious and Charitable Matters; Quantity of Real Property Trustees May Hold (Box 36, Folder 74)
- SB 945 (01) VRS Benefits (Box 36, Folder 75)
- SB 946 (01) Assistant Voter Registrars; Residency Requirements (Box 36, Folder 76)
- SB 949 (01) VRS; Surviving Spouses Remarrying (Box 36, Folder 77)
- SB 950 (01) Agricultural Cooperative Association; Forfeiture of Equity (Box 36, Folder 78)
- SB 954 (01) Teachers and Administrative Personnel; Returning to Work After Returning (Box 36, Folder 79)
- SB 955 (01) Health Insurance; Adverse Decisions (Box 36, Folder 80)
- SB 956 (01) Benefits of Town Council Members and Mayors (Box 36, Folder 81)
- SB 957 (01) Regional Industrial Facility Authorities (Box 36, Folder 82)
- SB 958 (01) Parking in Greene County (Box 36, Folder 83)
- SB 960 (01) Citizens' Advisory Council on Furnishing and Interpreting the Executive Mansion (Box 36, Folder 84)
- SB 962 (01) Department of Employee Dispute Resolution; Reversal of Grievance Hearing Decisions (Box 36, Folder 85)
- SB 963 (01) VRS; Coordination of Benefits (Box 36, Folder 86)
- SB 964 (01) Combined Precinct Registered Voter List and Pollbook; Study (Box 36, Folder 87)
- SB 967 (01) Licensure of Home Health Organizations; Exemptions (Box 36, Folder 88)
- SB 970 (01) ABC; Amphitheater Mixed Beverage License (Box 36, Folder 89)
- SB 972 (01) Landlord and Tenant; Access to Television Facilities (Box 36, Folder 90)
- SB 974 (01) Expert Witnesses (Box 36, Folder 91)
- SB 976 (01) Sales Tax Exemptions; Spaceport Activities (Box 36, Folder 92)
- SB 979 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 36, Folder 93)
- SB 983 (01) Commission on Alcohol Safety Action Program (VASAP) (Box 36, Folder 94)
- SB 984 (01) Search Warrants (Box 36, Folder 95)
- SB 986 (01) Recounts Involving Punch Card Voting Devices (Box 36, Folder 96)
- SB 987 (01) Insurance; Definition (Box 36, Folder 97)
- SB 989 (01) Indecent Liberties with Children; Penalty (Box 37, Folder 1)
- SB 990 (01) Suspension of Judges (Box 37, Folder 2)
- SB 992 (01) National Crime Information Center; Reports of Arrests (Box 37, Folder 3)
- SB 998 (01) Assault and Battery of a Correctional Officer (Box 37, Folder 4)
- SB 1001 (01) Limited Liability Companies; Limited Partnerships, etc. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- SB 1003 (01) Statewide Recycling Program (Box 36, Folder 6)
- SB 1006 (01) Spot Blight Abatement (Box 37, Folder 7)
- SB 1007 (01) Health; Newborn Testing (Box 37, Folder 8)
- SB 1008 (01) Child Day Care Funding for Low-Income Families (Box 37, Folder 9)
- SB 1012 (01) Conservation Land Foundation; Funds for Natural Area Protection (Box 37, Folder 10)
- SB 1013 (01) Motor Vehicle Warranty Obligations (Box 37, Folder 11)
- SB 1014 (01) Modification of Spousal Support Awards (Box 37, Folder 12)
- SB 1017 (01) Computer Information as Used in Consumer Protection Act (Box 37, Folder 13)
- SB 1019 (01) Guidelines to Electronic Transactions Act's Implications on State Agencies (Box 37, Folder 14)
- SB 1022 (01) School Emergency Plans; Preservation of Student Transcripts (Box 37, Folder 15)
- SB 1023 (01) Information Providers Network Authority; Powers and Duties (Box 37, Folder 16)
- SB 1024 (01) Public Procurement Act; Procurement by Reverse Auctioning (Box 37, Folder 17)
- SB 1025 (01) Lists of Registered Voters and Persons Voting (Box 37, Folder 18)
- SB 1026 (01) Elections; Final Day for Voter Registration (Box 37, Folder 19)
- SB 1027 (01) Assistant Voter Registrars; Residency Requirements (Box 37, Folder 19)
- SB 1029 (01) Fire Prevention Code; Enforcement by Locality (Box 37, Folder 21)
- SB 1031 (01) Crime Commission is a Criminal Justice Agency (Box 37, Folder 22)
- SB 1032 (01) Suspension of School Employees for First Drug Offense (Box 37, Folder 23)
- SB 1033 (01) Public School Authority; Bonds and Notes for Grants (Box 37, Folder 24)
- SB 1034 (01) Prisoners Permitted to Work on Certain Property (Box 37, Folder 25)
- SB 1036 (01) Issuance of Governor's Warrant of Arrest (Box 37, Folder 26)
- SB 1039 (01) Pre-sentence Reports in Sex Offense Cases (Box 37, Folder 27)
- SB 1040 (01) Pro Tempore Judges (Box 37, Folder 28)
- SB 1042 (01) Small Business Advisory Board; Membership (Box 37, Folder 29)
- SB 1043 (01) Veterinary Inspection for Ornamental Aquarium Fish or Invertebrate Animals (Box 37, Folder 30)
- SB 1044 (01) Industrial Hygiene and Safety Title Protection Act; created (Box 37, Folder 31)
- SB 1045 (01) Secondary Highways; Resumption of Responsibilities by Counties (Box 37, Folder 32)
- SB 1046 (01) Assistant Commissioner for the Environment, Transportation Planning (Box 37, Folder 33)
- SB 1047 (01) Statewide Transportation Plan (Box 37, Folder 34)
- SB 1048 (01) Management of the Commonwealth's Central Vehicle Fleet (Box 37, Folder 35)
- SB 1049 (01) Powers and Duties of the Commonwealth Transportation Board (Box 37, Folder 36)
- SB 1050 (01) Value Engineering in Highway Projects (Box 37, Folder 37)
- SB 1051 (01) Highway Projects Cancelled by Counties (Box 37, Folder 38)
- SB 1052 (01) VDOT Contracts (Box 37, Folder 39)
- SB 1052 (01) VDOT Contracts (Box 37, Folder 39)
- SB 1055 (01) Career and Technical Education (Box 37, Folder 40)
- SB 1056 (01) Standards of Learning; Substitution of Certain Tests (Box 37, Folder 41)
- SB 1057 (01) Educational Technology in Career and Technical Education Programs (Box 37, Folder 42)
- SB 1059 (01) Health Professions; Regulation of Clinical Psychologists (Box 37, Folder 43)
- SB 1062 (01) Adoption of Water Supply Emergency Ordinances (Box 37, Folder 44)
- SB 1069 (01) Gift Certificates; Larceny (Box 37, Folder 45)
- SB 1071 (01) VRS; Additional Accidental Death and Dismemberment Benefits (Box 37, Folder 46)
- SB 1072 (01) Reporting of Ballast Water Discharge; Penalty (Box 37, Folder 47)
- SB 1077 (01) VRS; Purchase of Prior Service Credit (Box 37, Folder 48)
- SB 1079 (01) Financial Institutions; Interest and Loan Limits (Box 37, Folder 49)
- SB 1080 (01) Public Accountancy Act (Box 37, Folder 50)
- SB 1085 (01) Joint Commission on Health Care (Box 37, Folder 51)
- SB 1086 (01) Admissions Tax; New Kent County (Box 37, Folder 52)
- SB 1087 (01) Chesapeake Bay 2000 Agreement Annual Report (Box 37, Folder 53)
- SB 1088 (01) Insurance Agents; Continuing Education (Box 37, Folder 54)
- SB 1090 (01) Underground Utility Damage Prevention Special Fund (Box 37, Folder 55)
- SB 1092 (01) Motor Carrier Service Centers (Box 37, Folder 56)
- SB 1095 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers; Damages Caused by Statutory Violations (Box 37, Folder 57)
- SB 1096 (01) Confidentiality of Public Assistance and Social Services Information (Box 37, Folder 58)
- SB 1097 (01) Vehicle Weight Limits; Liquidated Damages, etc. (Box 37, Folder 59)
- SB 1098 (01) Recodification of Titles 2.1 and 9, etc. (Box 37, Folder 60)
- SB 1100 (01) ABC; Special Motor Sports Road Racing Licenses (Box 37, Folder 61)
- SB 1102 (01) Insurance; Confidentiality of Information (Box 37, Folder 62)
- SB 1103 (01) Mortgage Brokers; Licensure (Box 37, Folder 63)
- SB 1107 (01) Election Districts and Voting Precincts (Box 37, Folder 64)
- SB 1109 (01) Semiconductor Manufacturing Performance Grant Programs (Box 37, Folder 65)
- SB 1110 (01) Transient Occupancy Tax; Mecklenburg County (Box 37, Folder 66)
- SB 1112 (01) Income Tax Credit for Machinery for Processing Recyclable Materials (Box 37, Folder 67)
- SB 1116 (01) Veterans Care Center; Board of Trustees (Box 37, Folder 68)
- SB 1117 (01) Thermal Imaging Camera Grant Fund (Box 37, Folder 69)
- SB 1120 (01) Donations to Roanoke Higher Education Authority (Box 37, Folder 70)
- SB 1122 (01) Tolling or Suspension of Statutes of Limitation (Box 37, Folder 71)
- SB 1124 (01) Location of Utility Easements (Box 37, Folder 72)
- SB 1127 (01) Reinstatement of Drivers' License After Drunk Driving Conviction (Box 37, Folder 73)
- SB 1128 (01) VASAP Case Manager's Oath of Office (Box 37, Folder 74)
- SB 1133 (01) Evaluation of Dealership Performance (Box 37, Folder 75)
- SB 1139 (01) Health; Scholarships and Loans for Health Professionals (Box 37, Folder 76)
- SB 1140 (01) Council on Human Resources (Box 37, Folder 77)
- SB 1142 (01) Elections; Change of Registered Voter's Address (Box 37, Folder 78)
- SB 1144 (01) Optional Education Programs for Kindergarten Through Grade Five (Box 37, Folder 79)
- SB 1150 (01) Motor Vehicles; License Fees (Box 37, Folder 80)
- SB 1154 (01) Community Policing (Box 37, Folder 81)
- SB 1159 (01) DMHMRSAS; Licensing (Box 37, Folder 82)
- SB 1160 (01) Office of Farmland Preservation (Box 37, Folder 83)
- SB 1161 (01) Entitlement to Certain Sales Tax Revenues (Box 37, Folder 84)
- SB 1162 (01) Recycling Markets Developing Council (Box 37, Folder 85)
- SB 1163 (01) Advisory Commission on Schools for Deaf and Blind (Box 37, Folder 86)
- SB 1164 (01) Regulation of Milk and Milk Products; Penalty (Box 37, Folder 87)
- SB 1166 (01) Definition of Impounding Structure (Box 37, Folder 88)
- SB 1167 (01) Conditional Release of Geriatric Prisoners (Box 37, Folder 89)
- SB 1170 (01) Virginia Tech/Montgomery Regional Airport Authority (Box 37, Folder 90)
- SB 1172 (01) Eminent Domain; Appraisals (Box 37, Folder 91)
- SB 1177 (01) Charitable Gaming Commission; Pull Tabs or Seal Cards (Box 38, Folder 1)
- SB 1178 (01) Modification of Sentencing Guidelines for Methamphetamine (Box 38, Folder 2)
- SB 1181 (01) Bodily Injuries to Prisoners, etc. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- SB 1182 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 38, Folder 4)
- SB 1187 (01) Agricultural or Forestry Product; Facility or Animal; Destroying (Box 38, Folder 5)
- SB 1190 (01) Youth Suicide Prevention; Study Report (Box 38, Folder 6)
- SB 1195 (01) Juvenile Justice Information System (Box 38, Folder 7)
- SB 1197 (01) Clerks and Deputy Clerks of General District Courts (Box 38, Folder 8)
- SB 1198 (01) Temporary Voter Registration Procedures for Presidential Elections (Box 38, Folder 9)
- SB 1199 (01) Adult Protective Services; Competency Training (Box 38, Folder 10)
- SB 1200 (01) Health Care Coverage; Infant Hearing Screenings (Box 38, Folder 11)
- SB 1201 (01) School; Preschool Physicals (Box 38, Folder 12)
- SB 1207 (01) Access to High Schools for Military Recruiters (Box 38, Folder 13)
- SB 1209 (01) Child Support Enforcement (Box 38, Folder 14)
- SB 1210 (01) World War II Veterans Appreciation Week (Box 38, Folder 15)
- SB 1211 (01) Abortion, Informed Written Consent as a Prerequisite; Penalty (Box 38, Folder 16)
- SB 1212 (01) Procurement; Faith-Based Organizations (Box 38, Folder 17)
- SB 1214 (01) Neighborhood Assistance Programs; Tax Credits (Box 38, Folder 18)
- SB 1217 (01) Absentee Ballots; Application for Disabled Voters; Study Report (Box 38, Folder 19)
- SB 1221 (01) Charter; City of Falls Church (Box 38, Folder 20)
- SB 1222 (01) School Crossing Guards (Box 38, Folder 21)
- SB 1224 (01) Fire Programs Fund (Box 38, Folder 22)
- SB 1225 (01) Absentee Voting Procedures (Box 38, Folder 23)
- SB 1227 (01) Fingerprinting of Fire Department Applicants in Arlington County (Box 38, Folder 24)
- SB 1228 (01) Affordable Housing in Arlington County (Box 38, Folder 25)
- SB 1229 (01) Landlord and Tenant Provisions in Northern Virginia (Box 38, Folder 26)
- SB 1232 (01) Virginia Resources Authority; Power to Borrow Money, etc. (Box 38, Folder 27)
- SB 1233 (01) Statewide Building Code; Effect on Local Ordinances (Box 38, Folder 28)
- SB 1236 (01) Driver's Licenses of Minors (Box 38, Folder 29)
- SB 1242 (01) Real Property Partial Exemptions and Tax Credits; Fees for Processing (Box 38, Folder 30)
- SB 1243 (01) Nontidal Wetlands; Effective Date (Box 38, Folder 31)
- SB 1244 (01) Political Advertisements (Box 38, Folder 32)
- SB 1245 (01) Geographic and Statewide Base Map Data; DTP to Report on Activities (Box 38, Folder 33)
- SB 1246 (01) Identity Fraud (Box 38, Folder 34)
- SB 1247 (01) Regulation of Land-Disturbing Activity (Box 38, Folder 35)
- SB 1250 (01) Pilot Project for Computerization of Local Septic System Data (Box 38, Folder 36)
- SB 1251 (01) Grants from Virginia Water Quality Improvement Fund (Box 38, Folder 37)
- SB 1254 (01) Official Fleet of the Commonwealth (Box 38, Folder 38)
- SB 1257 (01) Electric Utility Restructuring; Eminent Domain (Box 38, Folder 39)
- SB 1259 (01) Sex Crimes with Children (Box 39, Folder 40)
- SB 1275 (01) Reporting Requirements of Campaign Finance Disclosure Act (Box 38, Folder 41)
- SB 1277 (01) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act; Reports of Contributions (Box 38, Folder 42)
- SB 1280 (01) Powers of Farmers Market Board (Box 38, Folder 43)
- SB 1285 (01) Discharges into State Waters; Notification Required (Box 38, Folder 44)
- SB 1286 (01) People with Disabilities (Box 38, Folder 45)
- SB 1290 (01) Board of Nursing Home Administrators (Box 38, Folder 46)
- SB 1291 (01) "Photo Toll" Toll Payment Photo-Monitoring Program (Box 38, Folder 47)
- SB 1295 (01) Telephone Privacy Protection Act (Box 38, Folder 48)
- SB 1296 (01) Duties of Court Services Units and Local Departments of Social Services (Box 38, Folder 49)
- SB 1297 (01) Matters within Jurisdiction of Environmental Agencies (Box 38, Folder 50)
- SB 1299 (01) "Pave-in-Place" Program (Box 38, Folder 51)
- SB 1301 (01) No-Discharge Zone on Smith Mountain Lake (Box 38, Folder 52)
- SB 1304 (01) Teacher Proficiency; Continuing Contract Status (Box 38, Folder 53)
- SB 1305 (01) Human Cloning (Box 38, Folder 54)
- SB 1306 (01) Possession or Transportation of Stun Weapons by Convicted Felons (Box 38, Folder 55)
- SB 1308 (01) Criminal Injuries Compensation Fund; Sexual Abuse Cases (Box 38, Folder 56)
- SB 1312 (01) Overhead Highway Obstructions (Box 38, Folder 57)
- SB 1315 (01) "No Wake" Buoys (Box 38, Folder 58)
- SB 1318 (01) Vehicles Used to Transport Municipal Solid Waste (Box 38, Folder 59)
- SB 1320 (01) Local Meals Tax (Box 38, Folder 60)
- SB 1321 (01) Comprehensive Services Act for At-Risk Youth and Families (Box 38, Folder 61)
- SB 1322 (01) FOIA; Exempts Certain Electronic Communications (Box 38, Folder 62)
- SB 1324 (01) School Accreditation and College Admission (Box 38, Folder 63)
- SB 1325 (01) Low-Income Housing Tax Credit (Box 38, Folder 64)
- SB 1328 (01) Underground Utility Damage Prevention Act; Notification Centers (Box 38, Folder 65)
- SB 1329 (01) Provisional Driver's License (Box 38, Folder 66)
- SB 1331 (01) Pledge of Allegiance (Box 38, Folder 67)
- SB 1332 (01) Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Commission (Box 38, Folder 68)
- SB 1334 (01) School Safety Audits (Box 38, Folder 69)
- SB 1337 (01) Mental Health; Possession of Firearms (Box 38, Folder 70)
- SB 1339 (01) Deer Fences (Box 38, Folder 71)
- SB 1340 (01) Advisory Commission on Schools for Deaf and Blind (Box 38, Folder 72)
- SB 1343 (01) Overweight Permits; Trucks Hauling Concrete (Box 38, Folder 73)
- SB 1344 (01) Siting of Landfills in Mecklenburg County (Box 38, Folder 74)
- SB 1347 (01) DCJS; Private Security Services Businesses; Exceptions (Box 38, Folder 75)
- SB 1348 (01) Pollutant Discharge Elimination Permit (Box 38, Folder 76)
- SB 1349 (01) Wireless Enhanced Public Safety Telephone Service Act (Box 38, Folder 77)
- SB 1350 (01) Comprehensive Services Act; Family Assessment and Planning Team (Box 38, Folder 78)
- SB 1353 (01) Protective Orders; Firearms (Box 38, Folder 79)
- SB 1356 (01) Victim Participation in Plea Agreements (Box 38, Folder 80)
- SB 1358 (01) Release of Deed of Trust (Box 38, Folder 81)
- SB 1359 (01) Student Discipline (Box 38, Folder 82)
- SB 1365 (01) Commission; Repeal of Inactive Groups (Box 38, Folder 83)
- SB 1366 (01) Storage and Testing of Certain Evidence, Writ of Actual Innocence (Box 38, Folder 84)
- SB 1367 (01) Physical Training (Box 38, Folder 85)
- SB 1370 (01) Economic Development Partnership (Box 38, Folder 86)
- SB 1375 (01) Roanoke Higher Education Authority and Center (Box 38, Folder 87)
- SB 1377 (01) Breast or Cervical Cancer Treatment for Certain Women (Box 38, Folder 88)
- SB 1378 (01) Advisory Council on the Future of Nursing in Virginia (Box 38, Folder 89)
- SB 1385 (01) Licensed Bed Capacity in Certain Hospitals (Box 38, Folder 90)
- SB 1386 (01) Air Emissions Banking Program (Box 38, Folder 91)
- SB 1387 (01) Local Gas Severance Taxes (Box 38, Folder 92)
- SB 1391 (01) Accreditation of Schools (Box 38, Folder 93)
- SB 1393 (01) Charter Schools (Box 39, Folder 1)
- SB 1394 (01) Computer Invasion of Privacy (Box 39, Folder 2)
- SB 1398 (01) Funeral Processions; Hazard Lights (Box 39, Folder 3)
- SB 1402 (01) Resources Authority; Funding of Public Safety Facilities (Box 39, Folder 4)
- SB 1404 (01) Permits for Private Sewerage Facilities; Waiver of Filing Requirements (Box 39, Folder 5)
- SB 1406 (01) Mechanics' Lien Agent; Building Permits (Box 39, Folder 6)
- SB 1408 (01) State Council of Higher Education; Appointment of Members (Box 39, Folder 7)
- SB 1409 (01) Sales and Use Tax Exemption (Box 39, Folder 8)
- SB 1410 (01) Coal and Gas Severance Tax and Road Improvement Tax (Box 39, Folder 9)
- SB 1413 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 39, Folder 10)
- SB 1415 (01) General Assembly; Office Expenses of Members (Box 39, Folder 11)
- SB 1416 (01) Income Tax Credit; Rainwater Harvesting (Box 39, Folder 12)
- SB 1419 (01) Property Transfer at College of William and Mary (Box 39, Folder 13)
- SB 1420 (01) Electric Utility Restructuring Act (Box 39, Folder 14)
- SB 1421 (01) Electricity and Gas Companies Local License Tax (Box 39, Folder 15)
- 2001 Special Session of the General Assembly (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Special Session - HB 1 (01) House of Delegates Districts (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Special Session - HB 15 (01) Longwood College; Facilitation of Funds for Restoration (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Special Session - HB 17 (01) Local Reapportionment; Prison Population (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Special Session - HB 18 (01) Congressional Districts (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Special Session - HB 21 (01) Charter; Town of Pocahontas (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Special Session - HB 22 (01) Real Estate Board; Exemption from Licensure (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Special Session - SB 1 (01) Senate Districts (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Special Session - SB 2 (01) Elections of Council Members Following Annexation (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Special Session - SB 9 (01) Congressional Districts (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Special Session - SB 10 (01) Data Reported to Board of Medicine (Box 39, Folder 26)
- 2001 General Assembly List of Bills Passed (Box 40, Folder 1)
- 2001 General Assembly List of Bills Approved or Enacted (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2001 General Assembly List of Bills Governor Vetoed (Box 40, Folder 3)
- 2001 General Assembly List of Bills Governor Amended (Box 40, Folder 4)
- HB 13 (01) Who are Conservators of the Peace (Box 40, Folder 5)
- HB 41 (01) Worker's Compensation; Includes ABC Special Agents (Box 40, Folder 6)